I am Lawrence go I'm 37 years old
I'm the person on a autism spectrum I'm
working as an employer relations
associate I belong to the human
resources department I do encoding and
treating jobs and I'm uploading some
files to the SharePoint I am doing
return to work order an end of contract
process I just learned a lot of
different applications and I learned
some of the HR related cases and I hope
make sure it is secured and it kept in
the right place I feel a part of the
family and I had fun with few friends
and I'm working with a different
environment one of our values in action
I'd say would be share your humanity
which leaders would not just you know
publish it say for branding but it's
really in their hearts that to make sure
that every one of us in the organization
it's not just conscious about it but we
are working for it to make sure that you
know inclusion is really there
ASB has helped us a lot on that by
conducting sessions of you know
awareness sensitivity training sessions
and it also gave us an opportunity
because leaders started to you know look
into this and started supporting us and
it was an overwhelming actually welcome
to the organization I think he did touch
lives of you know few people that he had
socialized with hopes of the future I
want to be hard as a higher position and
I want to become a teacher and someday I
want to contribute to our society
[Music]